"You mark the journey of life"
"You are my destination"
"I can't imagine a life without you"
"You're the epicentre of my universe"
"You are always in my prayers"
"I can't imagine a life without you"
"Your absence propels me to my nemesis"
"To fill up the lacuna engulfing me, your presence is imperative"
"To be worthy of you, is all I crave for"
"I can't imagine a life without you"
"You rule my heart and my soul"
"As I bask in the glory of losing myself to you"
"Though you have subjected me to heart-rending pain"
"I cherish it"
"Considering it a reward from you"
"My world seeks refuge in the Midas' touch of your affection"
"To fill up the lacuna engulfing me, your presence is imperative"
"If not in this vile world"
"Unite with me in the sphere that is forsaken"
"I can't imagine a life without you."
We can't choose when to fall in love...
Loving someone is not in our hands
but going away from our loved one definitely is.
But we can choose when to walk away...